

Soniya Bastola

Head of Business Development, AIESEC in Kathmandu University

I am a sophomore in Kathmandu University with over three years of experience in working for social cause and leadership. Currently, I intend to develop myself and learn various skills while giving back to the society at the same time.

xoniyabastola2001@gmail.com

Phulikhel, Nepal

in linkedin.com/in/soniya-bastola-b89328214

+9779846002140

iii 09 September, 2001

WORK EXPERIENCE

Head of Business DevelopmentAIESEC in Kathmandu University

02/2022 - Present

Partnership and Communication Manager

TEDxKathmanduUniveristy

02/2022 - 04/2022

Event Head Youth Speak Forum 2022

03/2022 - 07/2022 AIESEC Nepal and CocaCola

Senior HR Manager

AIESEC in Kathmandu University

08/2021 - 01/2022

Business Development Associate

AIESEC in Kathmandu University

02/2021 - 07/2021

Project Manager

Rural Immersion Project

09/2018 - 10/2018 St. Xavier's College, Maitighar

EDUCATION

B.Tech in Biotechnology

Kathmandu University, School of Science

02/2021 - Present Dhulikhel, Nepal

High School

St. Xavier's College, Maitighar

08/2017 - 05/2019 Kathmandu, Nepal

Primary and Secondary School

Gandaki Boarding School

05/2010 - 04/2017 Pokhara, Nepal

SKILLS



LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Nepali

Full Professional Proficiency

Hindi

Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Event Management Content Writing Dancing

Travelling Community Involvement

Youth Leadership Public Speaking